Guide to Bloomsburg State College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00226
Cubberley Education Library
Bloomsburg State College (later: Bloomsburg University of Pennsylvania; formerly: Bloomsburg State Teachers College; formerly: Bloomsburg State Normal School; formerly: Bloomsburg Literary Institute and State Normal School)
1889-1977
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00226
50 item(s)
Located in Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania. Founded in 1839 as Bloomsburg Academy. Underwent a variety of name changes over the years: Bloomsburg Literary Institute (1856), Bloomsburg Literary Institute and State Normal School (1869), Bloomsburg State Normal School (1916), Bloomsburg State Teachers College (1927), Bloomsburg State College (1960), and Bloomsburg University of Pennsylvania in 1983.
Pennsylvania; Teachers colleges
- Bloomsburg Literary Institute and State Normal School, 1889-1914; 17 item(s) Catalogs for 1889/90-1890/91, 1892/93, 1895/96, 1897/98-1904/05, 1909/10-1913/14
  - Bloomsburg Literary Institute and State Normal School: Commercial Department, 1904; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1904
  - Bloomsburg State Normal School Quarterly, January 1910; 1 item(s)
- Bloomsburg State Normal School, 1916-1927; 5 item(s) Catalogs for 1916/17, 1919/20, 1922/23, 1925/26-1926/27
- Bloomsburg State Teachers College, 1927-1946; 18 item(s) Catalogs for 1927/28-1928/29, 1930/31-1945/46
  - Bloomsburg State Teachers College: Business Education Announcement, April 1938; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1938
  - Bloomsburg State Teachers College: General Information Circular, 1938-1939; 1 item(s) Circular for 1938/39
  - Bloomsburg State Teachers College: Editor Answers Some Questions Asked by High School Students, 1938; 1 item(s)
- Bloomsburg State College, 1963-1977; 4 item(s) Catalogs for 1963/64, 1969/70, 1975/76
  - Bloomsburg State College, 1976-1977; 1 item(s) Bulletin for 1976/77